All right, the next thing that you want to be careful about is humor.
As always, my rule is if you're not funny don't try to be.
However, you might think you're funny, because you're a little intoxicated.
But be very careful about the humor that you use, especially if you're using humor at someone else's expense, like we talked about in the last clip.
You have to keep in mind, and I know I keep saying this over and over, but you have to keep in mind that whatever you say is going to be filtered through potentially inebriated guests.
So, be real careful about humor, because some humor, depending on the situation, and the way in which you use it could end up being offensive.
You don't want to overuse humor either.
You might make one funny statement, or one funny joke, but don't let it be applicable to any specific situation.
However; on the other hand, because your guests could potentially be inebriated, this could be that you've been saving up this really funny line that you've been wanting to use for ten years.
Well, you might, based on the situation, throw it out there, because they're probably not going to remember the speech two minutes after you're done anyway.